

Profile

Full Stack Developer at Tietoevry Care, specializing in cloud-native, Al-powered healthcare solutions. Contributed to Finland's largest healthcare data platform (HUS DataLake), improving data accessibility. Proficient in **React**, **TypeScript**, **GraphQL**, **Node.js**, **Docker**, **Kubernetes**, **Terraform**, and **Azure Cloud**. Worked on LLM-based Al prototypes, including a demo at ICT Days and a diagnostic tool piloted at the New Children's Hospital for faster symptom-based searches.

Employment History

Full Stack Developer, Tietoevry, Espoo

JUNE 2023 - PRESENT

Developing cloud-native, Al-powered healthcare applications for Finland's largest healthcare providers. Working with React, TypeScript, Node.js, GraphQL-, PostgreSQL, Docker, Kubernetes, Terraform, Azure Cloud and Azure DevOps in Agile Scrum teams.

Key contributions:

- Contributing to the <u>HUS DataLake</u> platform for real-time healthcare data access
- Built an <u>AI PoC</u> to assist doctors in faster diagnosis via medical document analysis
- Developed an <u>LLM-based AI solution for ICT Days</u>, Finland's largest healthcare tech event

Junior Full Stack Developer, Anyhau, Espoo

DECEMBER 2022 - APRIL 2023

Worked on a greenfield web <u>application for booking animal-related services</u>, in collaboration with the 2022 Diili show winner. For providers to list services, and customers to book & pay online. Used **Next.js**, **Typscript**, **Material UI**, and **MongoDB**.

Education

Computer Programming, Hive Helsinki, Helsinki

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

Completed a project-based program focused on teamwork, problem-solving, and self-directed learning. Built skills in collaboration, critical thinking, and adaptability for real-world software development.

Interesting projects which I am proud of:

- My most favourite project is made in a group of four people. A re-creation of Netflix - <u>Hypertube</u>
- My second favourite project is made in duo, full-stack, a re-creation of Tinder -Matcha
- My third is made in solo, full-stack, a re-creation of Instagram, fully functional and deployed! **CHECK OUT**

A2 finnish language skill, SataEdu, Rauma

NOVEMBER 2016 - JULY 2017

Self-studied Finnish after school now converse comfortably and keep improving.

Certificate

Azure Fundamentals AZ-900, Microsoft

JULY 2023 - AUGUST 2023

Personal Details

Espoo

Finland

+35844-989-4822

gaborulenius@gmail.com

Links

My Portfolio

Linkedin

GitHub

Mangofruit - Live project

Technical skills / Programming Languages

Languages

React, Next.js, Node.js

Typescript

GraphQL

HTML5, CSS, Javascript Vanilla

PHP

С

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB,

MariaDB

Terraform

Soft Skills

Teamwork

Creative Problem Solving

Critical Thinking

Communication

Growth Mindset

Adaptability

Accountability

Customer Service

Efficiency

Time management

Organization & rigor

Tools

Azure DevOps, Azure Cloud GitHub, Gitlab & Git, CI/CD

pipelines

Docker

Kubernetes

Asana, Atlassian, Jira,

Confluence, Miro

MAMP, XAMPP, LAMP

MyphpAdmin, pgAdmin,

DataGrip, Postico 2, DBeaver

Mongoose

Postman

Lucidchart

Bulma, MUI, Tailwind

Redux, Recoil, Jotai

VS Code, Vim, CLI, Termux,